This is Trigun.
Oh, my God.
Why, Meryl, the ride is comfy, isn't it?
It sure is.
This is one incredible piece of machinery.
The only way it could be better
is if it were a little bit faster.
Now that would be dreamy.
I'm doing the best I possibly
can. Give me a break.
My goodness, Meryl, this
car can actually talk.
There's no way, Millie.
You're just hearing things.
Gee, I hope you're right.
These girls only care about themselves.
Do you have any right to say
that after wrecking our car?
I think not you're gonna
take full responsibility
Oh, my God.
Look, it's the Roderick thieves.
Yeah, but who are those girls?
They must be captives.
They really make me sick.
Hey, liquor boy, bring us
the best booze in the house.
I'm thirsty.
Come here, come here, right away, sir.
Ah!
Bang!
Ain't this fun?
Hey, that guy, how long
has he been sitting there?
Beats me.
You bitch, you were looking at him.
You know I can't stand
it when you do that.
I can't stand it.
How dare you disrespect me?
What do you think?
He's better than me, do you?
Do you?
All right, Nagi, that's enough.
But she was looking right at him.
You don't stand a chance
against him anyway.
It's too bad.
Looks like a lady-killer, the
kind the women all go after.
Well, Mr.
Handsome, that's real cruel of you.
You see, these girls are too delicate.
Last night they gave
up everything they had.
Their families, their
lovers, their entire past.
How can you just sit there
reminding them of what they lost?
What a waste of time.
Now we'll have to help them forget
it all over again, won't we, huh?
You listening, slick? What do you think?
You're too good for us?
Hey, punk!
You're not paying attention!
A fork, please. Asshole!
It's not wise to be hasty.
I intend to eventually
destroy all of mankind
right down to the very
last speck of dust yet.
Why is it that you insist
upon meeting our death sooner?
You don't make any sense.
You're just talking a bunch of nonsense.
It doesn't matter. Huh?
You volunteered first, that's all.
What the hell are you doing?
It's simple.
You're the first to die.
It hurts!
Make it down!
Your turn!
But why?
What the hell are you doing?
I can't stop it!
I can't put it down!
Dammit, bastard!
Please! Stop it!
Don't kill me!
It really is a shame what happened to you,
but now at least you
know just how much pain!
There is in living.
The day it all ends is near!
I advise you to make good use
of the time you have left.
That's unusual for me.
I don't usually waste my
time on vermin like that.
It must be the way you
look, Vash the Stampede.
Your very existence seems to
cause me undue irritation.
At last, we're finally here.
You look bad. Are you all right?
How can you even have
the nerve to ask me that?
I'm alive again!
Boy, that was really close!
Well, I think I'll have a drink
somewhere to perk myself up.
Where's the nearest saloon?
I'm thirsty.
I know there's gotta be
one somewhere around here.
Other than Mr.
Vash, this city certainly
is quiet, isn't it?
I guess I was right before.
Oh, look!
Here's one right here!
I'm going in!
Hi!
What's the matter?
Uh, nothing, really.
Nothing at all.
Who?
Who did this?
There are a lot of you, aren't there?
You're planning to move in for the kill.
I find it awfully hard to believe that the
Vice Chief was killed by a fool like you.
So what kind of trick did
you pull on him anyway?
Humans, how pathetic.
Shut your mouth!
The Rodericks are bound by
bonds that go infinitely
deeper and stronger than a
simple family relationship.
We will avenge our brethren,
no matter who the fool is.
That's the Roderick way.
This here is goodbye, Ladykiller.
What in the world?
Wait, Commander, I don't
know what's going on!
What are you doing, idiot?
Let go of me now!
My hands!
They're moving all by themselves!
Cut the crap!
You gotta believe me!
Such fragile bombshell.
I'm not doing this!
What the hell's the matter with you?
Really? Stop it!
I can't stop it!
Yes, you have a point.
It's just nice to be so greedy.
You're always talking to yourself!
It doesn't have to be all of them.
Just kill half of them this time round.
What the hell are you waiting for?
Watch your counteroffensive!
Why do you think I spared
half your men, Commander?
My reason happens to
be perfectly rational.
You see, if your bonds are
indeed deeper than family,
then you must have the opportunity
to give your friends a proper burial.
However, this is not an act of mercy.
This is to teach you the pain of living.
Excellent work, Commando.
Gray, the Nine Lives.
Dominic, the Cyclops.
Zazie, the Beast.
Luanoff, the Puppet Master.
Hopart, the Gauntlet.
Ryday, the Blade.
E .G. Mine.
Kane, the Longshot.
And myself, your faithful
Mid-Valley the Horn Freak.
We all offer you our support.
The chapel appears to be absent.
He seems to be as untrustworthy
as the rumors claim.
It doesn't matter much.
Your target is very close by.
It shouldn't be any problem.
There's a great deal of talent here.
You planning to use all
of us on this one target?
Hardly.
I would never waste all
that talent on one target.
My respect for you is higher than that.
Wouldn't you agree, Dominique?
Yes, I'm all you need for this job.
Legato, I'll take care of it.
I need to ask you something!
Open the door!
Wait, Vash, what's wrong?
Wait, please, I mean you no harm!
If you tell me who did
this, we can stop him.
Was it Legato that did it?
Tell me, was he wearing a white coat?
I don't feel sorry for you one bit.
It's your own fault for trying to force
your way into a private residence.
He's somewhere in this town.
I'm sure of it. But where?
Where?
You're awfully quiet.
Does your finger really hurt that much?
Why, that's filthy!
Are you crazy or something?
What's gotten into you?
What is he up to this time?
We're being left behind.
He was so tired a moment
ago, I don't understand him.
Should I shoot him?
Would you put that down?
Corpses.
you're naive had I been so
inclined I could have killed you at
least three times by now it would
seem that you enjoy dropping in on
people just to stir them up fun
hobby lady who are you one of the
gung-ho guns are you on legato's
team i suppose that's one way of
looking at it i'm the second
gung-ho gun i'm known as dominique
the cyclops is this your doing that's
right i merely took out some of
the trash they just use people in
order to line their own pockets call
it a spring cleaning of sorts well
does that make you feel any better
you killed them even though
they did terrible things
the decision of who should
and should not live was never
yours to make I should slap
you not to mention that during
this conversation I could
have groped you at least five
Okay, so let's say maybe four times.
Well, what now?
Shall we fight? Of course.
You decided to up the ante
and I'm not going to fold.
At least not before looking at the cards.
Now that wouldn't be fair.
I wouldn't do this if I were you.
I don't want to hurt you.
What blind optimism.
It's easy to see why your understanding of
fighting is so simplistic
and unsophisticated.
You had some success
with your barbaric style,
but this is the last day you'll
be saved by a simple, quick draw.
Checkmate.
That's very cute.
What kind of freak are you lady that was
definitely not human
you're an unpredictable Man
gunfighter i actually like your type me
unpredictable i'm not the
one teleporting all Over
the place i'll compliment
you upon countering
my attack twice but just how long Do you
think you can keep it up go ahead and try
again if you like but
you'd better shoot me this
time.
That's no empty threat.
Unfortunately, she holds
the card of maneuverability.
I have to find
a way to take her down.
Look.
Look at her. Look hard.
She's going to move.
Don't you dare miss it.
You're very confident, gunman.
But it is to no avail.
Like I told you, you can't beat me.
It It really doesn't
matter how fast you are.
You see?
I can't follow her.
You're a very sloppy gunfighter.
That makes it three times
that you've made me miss.
I'm sloppy.
You're the one who missed.
I'm using all of my senses.
And when she moves,
it's like she vanishes.
How can that be?
How can she move that fast?
She did it then.
And then.
Oh, I get it.
Have you rested enough?
I would like to end the show
soon if it's all the same to you.
Well, have you given up?
Or are you playing at some
kind of pathetic martial art?
It's not.
Not possible. Impossible.
But how how did you do that you numb the
perceptions of your opponent
through hypnotic charm
The spell somehow comes from
your eye that's the card you
hold the demon's eye should affect
All five senses whether your
eyes are opened or closed so how
what are you saying you escaped
the demon's eye by focusing all
of your concentration on pain?
Don't screw with me.
No mortal could possibly do that.
Die!
Game's over.
Instead of spending
time cleaning up people,
you should be cleaning
house for the man you love.
Like me for example I am kidding you
know what
are you doing get this poor
defenseless woman you animal did you see
anything that was going on here at all?
Are you all right come
on what are you doing?
This isn't over Vash the Stampede it
would be nice if you were addressed the
next time
I thought
I thought that I
was dead I can't believe he saw through
the demons eye I can't believe I was
beaten by that feather
brain of
a man mr. Dr.
Vash, I want an explanation of just
exactly what went on here today.
What was that?
It's time to decide, huh?
I'm sorry, but this is as far
as we can travel together. Why?
Because it's become too dangerous.
I'm afraid I have to go.
I have no choice.
We have a job to do.
It's your job or your life.
Which is more important to you?
I can't explain now.
If I did, you'd be put in danger.
So it's been a lot of fun,
but well, I guess that's all.
Stay back.
Is it
possible
that this was?
all a farce just to get me riled?
If so, I will turn the tables.
Legato, this time
it's my turn to hunt you.
I'll find you.
Whatever it takes.
A fragment of memory lost in
the gap between life and death?
Is it something which will point
the way to spiritual awareness?
The silver metallic gun crushes,
and my right arm metamorphoses.
My past, my people, my mother.
The moment I was reunited with everything
I ever protected, the light took Augusta.
The humanoid typhoon, the 60 billion
double dollar man, bashed the stampede.
This is the beginning of my past.
This is the end of my journey.